<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book-reports on maoxunxing&#39;s life</title>
    <link>/en/book-reports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book-reports on maoxunxing&#39;s life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:05:59 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/book-reports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamb in His Bosom</title>
      <link>/en/book-reports/lamb-in-his-bosom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:05:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/book-reports/lamb-in-his-bosom/</guid>
      <description>It is mainly a depiction of farmers living in Georgia, USA, before the outbreak of the Civil War. They were not plantation owners, nor were they capitalists. Just ordinary people living on a piece of land, needing to feed themselves, fighting against the harsh living conditions, working hard for the need to feed their families, for their families and children, reflecting the different fates of each person, living a cold and warm life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Genius Girlfriend - The Naples Quartet</title>
      <link>/en/book-reports/my-genius-girlfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 17:30:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/book-reports/my-genius-girlfriend/</guid>
      <description>Overall, around the two women as the main line, with the changing times of those who happen to love, friendship, family matters, pay attention to the psychological description, delicate and fascinating. While people are almost always wrapped up in the context of the times in their lives, Leila maintains an independent personality with different character qualities. Leila comes out of the times and influences her community with her tenacious qualities and smart, independent personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vortex - Representative works of Junji Ito</title>
      <link>/en/book-reports/vortex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/book-reports/vortex/</guid>
      <description> Divided into two volumes, it is a classic Japanese horror manga. To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m a bit uncomfortable with this genre.
This book looks all write whirlwind, actually a bit of realistic allegory. Mainly reflects the current situation of Japanese people under the economic problems of Japan at that time. When everyone is tied to capital, humanity is lost, society becomes deformed&amp;hellip;
What I Liked  Reacts to the problems in society through abstraction ♪ The storytelling is stronger  ♪ What I Disliked  Look a little horror movie feeling  Key Takeaways  Be wary of capital and be an independent and free soul  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>